A Finding Aid to the Architectural League of New York Records, 1880s-1974, bulk 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archleag
Archives of American Art
- Exhibitions, 1887-1972, bulk 1930s-1960s; Series 5; 21.85 Linear feet Boxes 62-83, 111; OVs 117-119
  - National Gold Medal Exhibitions, 1930s, 1949-1965; 5.4
    - 1951 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 75)
      - Mural Painting, Correspondence (Apr. 30 - May 25, 1951) (Box 75, Folder 43)
      - Mural Painting, Jury, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 44)
      - [Mural] Painting, Submissions Accepted, circa 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 45)
      - [Mural] Painting, Submissions Returned, circa 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 46)
      - Publicity, 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 47)
      - Sculpture, Correspondence (Mar. 12 - Apr. 6, 1951), 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 48)
      - Sculpture, Jury, 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 49)
      - Sculpture, Preliminary Submissions, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 50)
      - Sculpture, Publicity, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 51)
      - Sculpture, Submissions Accepted, circa 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - [1952] Gold Medal Catalog, Advertising Contracts, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - 1952 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 75)
      - All Juries, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 54)
      - Architectural Works, Acceptances, circa 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 55)
      - Architectural Works, Rejections, circa 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 56)
      - Architecture, circa 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 57)
      - Architecture, Jury, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 58)
      - Architecture, Publicity, circa 1952 (Box 75, Folder 59)
      - Circular of Information, 1951-1952; (2 folders) (Box 75, Folder 60-61)
      - Circular of Information Requests by Individuals, circa 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 62)
      - Circular of Information Requests by Societies, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 63)
      - Citations, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 64)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, #2, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 65)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Jury, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 66)
      - Engineering, Submissions, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 67)
      - Final Gold Medal Dinner (June 12, 1952) (Box 75, Folder 68)
      - Final Gold Medal Exhibition, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 69)
      - Invitation to Medallists Dinner in Painting (June 12, 1952) (Box 75, Folder 70)
      - Invitation to Medallists Dinner in Sculpture (June 12, 1952) (Box 75, Folder 71)
      - Jurors, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 72)
      - Landscape Architecture, Submissions, 1951-1952 (Box 75, Folder 73)
    - 1952 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 76)
      - Mural Painting, Acceptances, circa 1951-1952 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Mural Painting, Citations, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Mural Painting, Correspondence re: Circular Distribution, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Mural Painting, Juror's Correspondence, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Mural Painting, Layouts for Exhibition, circa 1951 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Mural Painting, Newspaper Clippings, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Mural Painting, Press Release Dinner Invitation, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - [Mural Painting], Rejections, circa 1951-1952 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Sculpture, circa 1951-1952 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Sculpture, Accepted, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Sculpture, Mailing List, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - [Sculpture], Publicity, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Sculpture, Rejections, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - 1953 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 76)
      - Architecture, Acceptances, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Architecture, Final, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 15)
      - Architecture, Jurors, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - Architecture, Miscellaneous, circa 1953 (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Architecture, Publicity, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Architecture, Rejections, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Architecture, Submissions, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Architecture and Engineering, Preliminary Dinner (Feb. 5, 1953), circa 1953 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Architecture and Engineering, Press Release, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Circular Mailing List for Architecture, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Circular Mailing List for Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Art, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Circular Mailing List for Engineering, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 25)
      - Circular Mailing List for Landscape Architecture, 1950-circa 1953 (Box 76, Folder 26)
      - Circular of Information, Draft and Final Copy, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 27)
      - Circular of Information, Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 76, Folder 28)
      - Citations and Awards, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 29)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 30)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Acceptances, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 31)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Final, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 32)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Jurors, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 33)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Publicity, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 34)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Rejections, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 35)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Submissions, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 36)
      - Engineering, Acceptances, circa 1953 (Box 76, Folder 37)
      - Engineering, Final, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 38)
      - Engineering, Jurors, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 39)
      - Engineering, Publicity, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 40)
      - Engineering, Rejections, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 41)
      - Final Gold Medal, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 42)
      - Gold Medal Dinner, circa 1953 (Box 76, Folder 43)
      - Gold Medal Dinner for Mural Decoration, Sculpture, Design and Crafts (Dec. 4, 1952) (Box 76, Folder 44)
      - Landscape Architecture, Acceptances, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 45)
      - Landscape Architecture, Jurors, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 46)
      - Landscape Architecture, Miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 47)
      - Landscape Architecture, Publicity, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 48)
      - Landscape Architecture, Rejections, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 49)
      - Landscape Architecture, Submissions, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 50)
      - Mailing Lists, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 51)
      - Mural Decoration, Final, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 52)
      - Mural Decoration, Jurors, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 53)
      - Mural Decoration, Mailing List, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 54)
      - Mural Decoration, Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 55)
      - Mural Decoration, Publicity, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 56)
      - Mural Decoration, Rejections, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 57)
      - Mural Decoration, Submissions, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 58)
      - Publicity, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 59)
      - Sculpture, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 60)
      - Sculpture, Acceptances, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 61)
      - Sculpture, Final, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 62)
      - Sculpture, Jurors, 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 63)
      - Sculpture, Mailing List for Circulars of Information, circa 1951- 1952 (Box 76, Folder 64)
      - Sculpture, Publicity, circa 1952 (Box 76, Folder 65)
      - Sculpture, Rejections, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 66)
    - 1953 National Gold Medal Exhibition, Sculpture, Submissions, circa 1952-1953 (Box 76, Folder 67)
    - 1954 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 76)
      - Architecture, circa 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 68)
      - Architecture, Jury, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 69)
      - Circular of Information, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 70)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, 1953-1955 (Box 76, Folder 71)
      - Engineering, circa 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 72)
      - Gold Medal Citations, 1954-1955 (Box 76, Folder 73)
      - Landscape Architecture, circa 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 74)
      - Mailing List, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 75)
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 76, Folder 76-77)
      - Mural Decoration, 1953-1954 (Box 76, Folder 78)
    - 1954 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 77)
      - Reviews of Exhibition, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Sculpture, 1952-1954 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Sculpture, Jury, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - (1954-1955) Miscellaneous Gold Medal Material, 1938, 1951-1956 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - 1955 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 77)
      - Architecture, Acceptances, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Architecture, Entries, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Architecture, Jury, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Architecture, Miscellaneous, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Circular of Information, Prices and Quotations, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence re: Eleanor LeMaire, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Design and Crafts, 1953-1955 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Design and Crafts, Acceptances, circa 1955 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Design and Crafts, Entries, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Design and Crafts, Jury, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Dinner Program and List of Exhibitors, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Engineering, Acceptances, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Engineering, Entries, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Engineering, Jury, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Engineering, Miscellaneous, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Gold and Silver Medals, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Gold Medal Dinner, circa 1955 (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Gold Medal Request, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - Landscape Architecture, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - Landscape Architecture, Acceptances, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - Landscape Architecture, Entries, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - Landscape Architecture, Jury, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - List of Exhibitors, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Mailing List, circa 1954 (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955; (4 folders) (Box 77, Folder 29-32)
      - Mural Decoration, 1953-1955 (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - Mural Decoration, Acceptances, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - Mural Decoration, Entries, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - Mural Decoration, Jury, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - Mural List, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 37)
      - Prices on Printing for Same, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 38)
      - Publicity Releases, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 39)
      - Sculpture, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 40)
      - Sculpture, Entries, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 41)
      - Sculpture, Jury, circa 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 42)
      - Telegrams Sent to Winners, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 43)
    - 1956 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 77)
      - Architecture, circa 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 44)
      - Architecture, Acceptances, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 45)
      - Architecture, Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 46)
      - Architecture, Entry Slips, circa 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 47)
      - Architecture, Rejects, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 48)
      - Circular of Information Data, 1955-1957 (Box 77, Folder 49)
      - Citations, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 50)
      - Decoration for Gold Medal Exhibition, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 51)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, circa 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 52)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Acceptances and Rejects, circa 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 53)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Correspondence, circa 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 54)
      - Design and Craftsmanship in Native Industrial Arts, Rejects, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 55)
      - Engineering, Acceptances, circa 1956 (Box 77, Folder 56)
      - Engineering, Rejects, 1955-1956 (Box 77, Folder 57)
    - 1956 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 78)
      - Expenses, 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Gold Medal Committee Chairman Walker O. Cain, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Gold Medal Dinner and Program, circa 1956 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Juries, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Landscape Architecture, 1955 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Landscape Architecture, Correspondence, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Landscape Architecture, Rejects, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Mailing Lists, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Mural Decoration, Acceptances, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Mural Decoration, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Mural Decoration, Rejects, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Sculpture, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Sculpture, Acceptances, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Sculpture, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Sculpture, Rejects, circa 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - 1957 National Gold Medal Exhibition, Correspondence With League Vice Presidents re: 1957 Exhibition, circa 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - 1958 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 78)
      - Acceptance and Rejection Letters, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Applications to Receive Circular, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Architecture, Acceptances, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 20)
      - Architecture, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 21)
      - Architecture, Jury, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 22)
      - Architecture, Rejections, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 23)
      - Architecture, Submission, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 24)
      - Chairman, Maurice Gauthier, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 25)
      - Circulars and Programs, 1956, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 26)
      - Citations, 1958; (Oversized materials housed in Box 111, Folder 4) (Box 78, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 28)
      - Design and Crafts, Acceptances, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 29)
      - Design and Crafts, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 30)
      - Design and Crafts, Jury, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 31)
      - Design and Crafts, Rejections, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 32)
      - Engineering, Acceptances and Rejections, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 33)
      - Engineering, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 34)
      - Engineering, Jury Selection, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 35)
      - Landscape Architecture, Acceptances, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 36)
      - Landscape Architecture, Jury of Selection, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 37)
      - Landscape Architecture, Rejections, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 38)
      - Mural Painting, Acceptances, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 39)
      - Mural Painting, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 40)
      - Mural Painting, Jury of Selection, 1956-1958 (Box 78, Folder 41)
      - Mural Painting, Rejections, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 42)
      - Sculpture, Acceptances, circa 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 43)
      - Sculpture, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 44)
      - Sculpture, Jury Selection, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 45)
      - Sculpture, Rejects, circa 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - 1959 National Gold Medal Exhibition, List of Organizations to be Invited to Submit to the 1959 Gold Medal Show, 1955-1958 (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - 1960 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 78)
      - "Achievement in the Building Arts", 1959 (Box 78, Folder 48)
      - Acknowledgements of Entry Fees for the Exhibition Entries, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 49)
      - Applications for Circulars, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 50)
      - Circular of Information, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 51)
      - Exhibits #1-6, 1959-1960; (6 folders) (Box 78, Folder 52-57)
      - Expenses, circa 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 58)
      - General, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 59)
      - "Hotels and Motels" Correspondence, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 60)
      - Letters of Rejection - Open Submission, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 61)
      - Postal Receipts for Photos, Open Submission, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 62)
    - 1960 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 79)
      - Preliminary Exhibitions, 1959-1960; (9 folders) (Box 79, Folder 1-9)
      - Subscriptions for Final Catalog, 1959-1960 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Thank You Letter to All Jurors, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - 1962 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 79)
      - Acceptances, 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 79, Folder 12-13)
      - Circular of Information, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Circular of Information, First Draft, 1960-1962 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Letters of Rejection, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Mural Painting, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Negative of Collaboration Medal, 1962; (Oversized material housed in Box 111, Folder 5) (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - Requests for Circulars of Information, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - 1962 National Gold Medal Exhibition Committee (Box 79)
      - Architecture, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - Engineering, Joel D. Marder, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - Landscape Architecture, Richard G. Guthridge, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 22)
      - Sculpture, Quen Lux, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - 1965 National Gold Medal Exhibition (Box 79)
      - Acceptances, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 24)
      - Catalog, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 79, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, Chairman, Paul F. Damas, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - Entry Slip, circa 1964 (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - Expenses, 1962, 1965; (2 folders) (Box 79, Folder 29-30)
      - Invitation to Exhibit, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 31)
      - Mailing List, 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 32)
      - Paid Bills, circa 1965 (Box 79, Folder 33)
      - Rejections, 1965-1966 (Box 79, Folder 34)
      - Sculpture, R. Crombach, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Awards and Honorable Mentions, 1954-1958; (2 folders) (Box 79, Folder 36-37)
    - Circular of Information Mailing List, 1950-1951 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Circulars of Information, 1949-1960s; (2 folders) (Box 79, Folder 39-40)
    - Circulars of Information and Lists, circa 1950s (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Citation Proofs, circa 1952-1955 (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Collaborative Medal Competition, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1951-1953; (2 folders) (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
    - Deposit Slips, circa 1962 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Costs: Catalog Costs, Income, Etc., 1959-1962 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Expenses, 1953-1956 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Expenses, 1960-1962 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Gold Medal Applicants, 1953-1956 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Gold Medal Awards Catalog (1950-1952) (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Gold Medal Catalog, 1952-1953 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Gold Medal Catalog Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Gold Medal Catalog Committee Members, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Gold Medal Catalog Deposit Slips, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Gold Medal Catalog Deposits, 1952-1953 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Gold Medal Catalog Exhibition Fund, Special No. 5 [Bank Book], 1952-1953 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Gold Medal Catalog and Financial Records, 1951-1962 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Gold Medal Catalog, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Gold Medal Committee, 1951-1955, 1963; (3 folders) (Box 80, Folder 17-19)
    - Gold Medal Committee, Catalog, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Gold Medal Committee, Notices of Meetings, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Gold Medal Exhibition, 1950s-1960 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Gold Medal Fees, 1961-1965 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Gold Medal Ledger (1953-1954) and Howard Myers Award, 1952-1956 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Gold Medal Ledger (1955-1956) and Birch Burdette Long Memorial Prize (1956), 1955-1958 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Letter to Mr. Butt From Mr. Price, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Medal of Honor Competition Announcement, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Medallic Art Gold Medal, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Minutes of Gold Medal Exhibition Meetings, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s, 1962-1965; (5 folders) (Box 80, Folder 30-34)
    - Miscellaneous and Correspondence, circa 1951-1953 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Expenses Acct., R. Stern, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Portfolio of the Work of Members of the National Society of Mural Painters, 1952-1953 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Proposed National Gold Medal Exhibition, 1960-1965 (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Publicity, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Requests for Circulars of Information, 1962-1965 (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Warren Displays, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - 1958 National Gold Medal Exhibition, Citations, (Oversized materials from Box 78, Folder 27) (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - 1962 National Gold Medal Exhibition, Negative of Collaboration Medal, (Oversized material from Box 79, Folder 18) (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - 1939 World's Fair, 1935-1939; 5.5
    1939 World's Fair subseries documents the League's involvement in organizing the New York World's Fair in 1939. Found is correspondence; brochures and other printed materials; questionnaires to architects for awarding commissions; and records of the collaborative council. Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Agenda for Collaborative Council Meeting (Aug. 18, 1937) (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Artists Coordination Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Board of Design Chairman, Stephen F. Voorhees, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Bulletins, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Collaborative Council After Jan. 31, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Collaborative Council (Box 81)
      - Booklets Returned From World's Fair Office, 1937-1939 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Chairman, A.F. Brinckerhoff, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Chairman of Council, 1936-1938 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Circulars, 1936-1938 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Consultants re: Painters, Sculptors - Endorsements, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Disbanding of Council - Also Final Report and Notice to Members of the Council, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Executive Committee, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Extra Lists of Professional Societies and Their Representatives, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Fees for Temporary Expenses, Mailings, Etc., 1936 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - List of Council Members and Executive Committee Members, 1935-1937 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Minutes (Revised), 1937 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1933-1938; (2 folders) (Box 81, Folder 19-20)
      - Notices of Meetings and Acknowledgements, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Questionnaires Sent to Board of Design (List and Correspondence With the Board), 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Receipts for Books Sent to Board of Design From N.S.S., M.P., A.I.D. and Others, 1936-1938 (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - Collaborative Council, Leon V. Solon, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Code and By-Laws, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Committee Meetings, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence With Fair Office re: "Competition Drawings" and Model for Fair, 1936- 1937 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence With George McAneny, 1935-1936 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence With Percy S. Straus, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence With Grover Whalen, New York World's Fair President, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - The Decorators Club, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Delegates (Letters re:), 1937 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Designer-Craftsmen, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Duplicate Lists and Questionnaires from Coordination Committee, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Invitations to Attend Dinners, Etc., 1936 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - J. Scott Williams' Memo re: Collaborative Council Meeting (Oct. 1937) (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Meetings (Joint and Others), 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 37)